Oladeji Anthony

FrontEnd Developer

Personal Statement

Frontend developer with 3 years tested experience in working with teams and companies to create and maintain a better code base for reusability. passionate about learning and development with a desire to apply skills on larger development team. Eager to tackle more complex problems and continue to find ways to maximize user efficiency.

Work History

Front End Developer Freelance

Diatech International, Lagos (FEBURARY 2020 - PRESENT)

- Designed and implemented web applications along with 3rd-party software integrations as a web team laison for all interdepartmental and customer-facing projects.
- Designed the frontend interface of an e-commerce website with React JS, Redux, Restful API and Material UI
- Developed the frontend interface of SaaS applications in React Js,
 TypeScript, GraphQL, and Redux with full user experience in 3 months.

Junior Front-End Developer Intern

Eryeol incorporation, Remote (JANUARY 2022 - AUGUST 2022)

- Designed and implemented the frontend interface of an eprocurement website along with the team members of the company for 5month using React JS, React Redux and Material UI
- Conducted Unit and Integration Tests to verify functionality of the eprocurement website with Jest and React Testing Library
- Led a team of 4 persons for an investigation on Africa's ecommerce software development best practices.

Education

Bachelor of Engineering; computer Engineering

University of Ilorin, Ilorin, Kwara State, Nigeria.

(OCTOBER 2020 - PRESENT)

Address

llorin, Kwara State, Nigeria 240242

Phone

+2348137459380

E-mail

Oladejianthony98@gmail.com

Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/oladejianthony

Github

github.com/OladejiAnthony

Skills

JavaScript

React JS

Redux

TypeScript

Tailwind CSS

Styled component

SASS

React Bootstrap

Framer Motion

Jest &

React Testing library

GraphQL

Restful API

Agile Development Practice